{"data":[{"question":"Male guppies, like many other male fish, are more color than females.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Male","b":"like","c":"are","d":"color","answer":"4","explain":" - Color-> colorful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"When rhinos take mud baths, the mud create a barrier to biting insects.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"the","c":"create","d":"biting","answer":"3","explain":" - Create-> creates","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"Benjamin Franklin, as an inventor, he had broad interests, mechanical skills, persistence, and a practical view of life.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"as an","b":"he","c":"persistence","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":" - He-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"In the stock market, the fluctuations in Standard and Poor 's 500 Index does not always conform to Dow Jones Averages.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"does","c":"always","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":" - Does-> do","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"A jellyfish, which isn't really a fish, it has no brain, no bones, and no face.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"isn't","b":"a","c":"it","d":"bones","answer":"3","explain":" - It-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"International trade, going traveling, and television have lain the groundwork for modern global life styles.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"going traveling","b":"have lain","c":"for","d":"styles","answer":"1","explain":" - Going traveling-> traveling","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"The most visible remind of the close relationship between the United States and France is the famous Statue of Liberty, which stands in New York harbor.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"remind","b":"between","c":"is","d":"which","answer":"1","explain":" - Remind-> reminder","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"A prism is used to refract white light so it spreads out in a continuous spectrum of colors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to refract","b":"so","c":"out","d":"of","answer":"1","explain":" to refract -> refracting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"Despite of rain or snow there are always more than fifty thousand fans at the OSU football games.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Despite of","b":"are","c":"thousand","d":"at","answer":"1","explain":" - Despite of-> despite","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"The prices of homes are as high in urban areas that most young people cannot afford to buy them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"as","c":"that","d":"afford to","answer":"2","explain":" - As-> so","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"}]}